# Kwok Ming Leung

San Mateo, CA (650)686-9930

<u>k4leung@ucsd.edu</u> <u>https://kwokmingleung.github.io</u> https://github.com/kwokmingleung

# **Summary**

I enjoy being a student of Computer Science, especially when I coding and learning algorithms. I am interested in studying the field of artificial intelligence in my last two years in the university. I am seeking a software engineering internship at summer 2020.

## Education

University of California, San Diego

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science La Jolla, California Expect to graduate at July 2020 GPA 3.44

#### **College of San Mateo**

College Degree Computer Science San Mateo, California 01/2016 - 06/2018 GPA 3.55

# **Employment History**

#### **Computer Engineering Research Internship**

San Francisco State University, San Francisco, California June 2018 – September 2018

- Implement a new user login page to the existing app by using Java and Firebase
- Created a website with instructions regarding to the application using JavaScript making it open source
- Integrating mobile and cloud computing for electromyography (EMG) and Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU) base neural machine Interface
- Anticipate the human motion intention in real time from wearable sensors and by using basic Machine Learning algorithms

#### **STEM Center Tutor**

Cañada College, Redwood City, California

August 2017 – May 2018

- Teaching and helping college students in Calculus, Java, and C++
- Teaching basic programming skill includes inheritance and data structure
- Providing students some related mini-lessons such as Optimization, Riemann Sum, Double Integrals and Integration by Parts
- Working with peer tutors and allocate our works

# **Projects**

### Plinko simulation

August 2019

- Implemented a simple plinko game simulation in HTML5 using a physics engine Matter.js
- Involved of p5.js framwork for drawings things

## iTunes Search Engine

May 2018

- Created a website allow the user to search the songs and artist in iTunes
- Mainly build by jQuery, JSON, combined with HTML and CSS

## **Professional Skills**

Java: Proficient
Python: Proficient
C++: Proficient
HTML, CSS: Proficient

JavaScript: Intermediate
R: Some projects
NumPy: Some projects
Pandas: Some projects